What was that all about, Inaba?
Iori is mine!
Stay away from her!
There is no reason for you to complain.
I made it clear that you
and Fujishima are rivals.
If you work hard enough,
you can rescue Iori from
Fujishima's clutches.
I set the scene for you.
I don't want to turn a
classmate into an enemy.
Everyone but you yourself is an enemy.
Huh?
Say, Taichi.
Aren't you in love with Iori?
Huh?
I-I'm in love with Nagase?
What makes you say that?
You've started to overreact
to everything.
I recall you being more of a stoic lump.
That's because the circumstances I've
been dealing with force me to!
I'm telling you to bag Iori before
Fujishima beats you to it.
Why do you keep pushing
me in that direction?
And Fujishima's a girl!
Facing adversity to save someone
fits you perfectly, doesn't it?
Right?
Selfless freak.
What's that supposed to mean?
Exactly what I said.
Why did you volunteer for
this painful exercise?
Nobody else wanted to participate,
so I had to volunteer
to make sure that no one
else would have to suffer.
Which confirms that you're
a selfless freak.
Why do you like pro wrestling?
It's the art of enduring.
In pro wrestling, it's not about who can
perform stronger and flashier moves.
Special moves can only be performed on
opponents who are able to endure them.
I'm a big fan of jobbers, who
let themselves get beat up.
Shut the hell up, wrestling fanboy.
You asked for an answer.
So, back to Iori.
Have you noticed yet?
She's the weakest link in StuCS.
I've never seen anyone so close
to completely breaking down.
Isn't that what you're looking for?
She needs someone to shield
her from the pain and hurt.
Sounds like a job for the
selfless freak, right?
Don't put words in my mouth.
I've never looked at her in that light.
I should probably mention that
Iori's in love with you.
Nah, that can't be right.
Weak reaction.
She needs someone to cling to.
Someone who will be there to
unconditionally support her.
Besides, you and Iori come
alive when you're together.
Really?
Well, it's your problem to work out.
Do whatever you want.
But...
I have a feeling that Iori's
in the most danger.
Danger?
This personality swapping business
could break any one of us eventually,
but she's the one who's taking the
brunt of the adverse effects.
Adverse effects...
But so far, we've only had to
deal with a few minor hiccups.
You don't have to be
so serious about it—
Are you an idiot?!
How can you be so optimistic?!
There's no question,
you're the most clueless one in our group!
Do you realize how hopeless
our current situation is?!
At any moment, any one of us could
be seriously hurt, completely broken!
Don't you understand?
Sorry...
Yeah...
No, I was too harsh.
I've been feeling grouchy after
everything that's happened.
Sorry.
Can you forgive me?
There's nothing to forgive.
You're absolutely right. It's okay.
W-Well, let's get back to work.
We'll never finish at this rate.
You're completely clueless.
Huh?
Your trash bag was blown
away by the wind.
Huh?
Wh-Why didn't you say something?!
Where'd it go?
Ah, there it is!
It was more entertaining this way.
Y-You see...
I'm always yelling at you
because I don't want to
admit how I truly feel,
but deep down...
Deep down, I truly love you, Aoki.
I'm sorry about springing
this on you now.
But I can't continue to lie to myself.
Please go out with me!
Did you record it?
I did.
Okay, switch!
Y-Yeah...
W-Well, I kinda...
U-Um...
I like you!
So would you please go out with me?
Yup, that was good!
I felt a twinge when I saw
the sharp, manly Inaba-chan
confess like a girl!
The first recording was probably
taken from one of your fantasies.
I know.
Man, I hope I can get her
to say those words one day.
Well, that should be enough for now.
I'll delete the video.
Hey, we're just getting started.
Let's take a few more
shots before the girls
come back from shopping.
We may never get a chance
like this again.
Right?
Yui! Grab the cell phones!
I'm on it!
It's hard to move around in this body!
Taichi, you need to exercise more!
W-Well, I kinda...
U-Um...
I like you!
So would you please go out with me?
I see that you boys were having fun.
Um, Inaba? What are you doing?
I'm getting ready to run
around campus buck naked.
P-Please stop, Inaba-chan!
If you do that, you'll be killing
any chance I have of leading
a normal life!
Die.
Wait, Inaba!
Inaba-san! If you kill my
chances at a normal life,
I may have to kill myself!
Silence! This is the
punishment you deserve!
Don't expect to survive
if you try that again.
Yes, ma'am!
We're very sorry.
I'm just as mad as she is.
I'll beat the crap out of
you if you try that again.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Iori isn't here yet?
Yeah, she had to leave
early for something.
Oh, hey.
I've been wondering about something.
Yui-san, are you scared of us?
Every time I'm Yui,
I start to shake whenever
there's a man around.
That's nonsense.
Why should I be scared
of a couple weaklings...
...like you?
U-Uh, Yui...
After all, I'm way stronger
than you guys are.
So...
So men don't scare me.
Sorry!
I kept telling you how I loved you,
but I never realized that
you were hurting.
I'm such a big idiot!
Yui!
Forget it.
I'll go help her calm down.
Inaba-chan...
You knew?
Yeah...
She was good at concealing her fear,
so I can't blame you for not noticing.
But she's got it pretty bad.
I can help her get back on her feet.
You guys will have to
take it from there.
I hate myself now.
Don't be too hard on yourself.
Her acting was good enough
to impress Inaba.
I mean, I didn't notice anything
when I was Kiriyama...
But in retrospect, there were signs.
When you look at StuCS,
Inaba-chan is always mad
and beats us up all the time.
Iori-chan likes to touch people.
Yui is an active girl,
so it seemed odd that
she never joined in.
You're pretty perceptive, Aoki.
We're talking about the girl I love.
You're still the same person you were,
even after this whole
personality swapping mess.
My policy is to enjoy life as I go.
That's all I expect,
and that will never change.
So I'm hoping that we'll be able to
look back at this body swapping
and laugh, one day.
But that doesn't seem likely anymore
now that I've hurt Yui.
Why am I getting all serious?!
This isn't me!
I'm starting to think that
you could really go places.
I know.
You know, I think you have a
better chance with Yui than I do.
You were saying nice
things about me earlier,
but you have way more
potential than I do.
What kind of potential
are we talking about?
Well, you're pretty clueless,
so you haven't realized
how incredible you are.
I have no idea where to go from here.
Yeah, how can we help Kiriyama?
See?
That's what makes you incredible!
You're thinking about how to help her.
You think on a higher level.
Well, it's not like I
have any great ideas.
It's scary because I can
see you pulling it off.
But if that happens, Yui
might fall for you?
What are you...
I need to call Yui and apologize!
Taichi, I won't let you beat me!
Really?
Sure. If that's what you want, Mom.
Do you like this group?
Hm, they're okay.
Actually, there's a pro wrestling
special on tonight!
After this show is over.
Right...
Kiriyama...
Yeah, is this Kiriyama?
U-Um, I was probably crying,
but don't let it concern you.
Actually, just forget it happened.
Kiriyama, can we meet up somewhere?
Sorry, I kinda went into a panic,
so your sister was a little freaked out.
She's been confused by my behavior.
Anyway...
Aoki called me right before we switched.
He kept apologizing.
Over and over.
I realized that you and Aoki would
probably start tiptoeing around me,
so we wouldn't be able to have
fun the way we used to.
That thought made me
feel sorry for myself.
Kiriyama, do you suffer
from androphobia?
Yes.
There must have been a cause.
Could you tell me what that was?
I should have known you would
get straight to the point.
You're the second person I've talked
to about this, after Inaba.
Back when I was in middle
school, I was almost raped.
Nothing happened though.
I fought back and managed to escape.
Still, this was back when I
practiced karate every day.
I won against every man I faced.
I was convinced that I could fend off
anyone who attacked me.
But when it really happened,
I barely managed to escape.
Did you know?
Men are incredibly strong.
That's when I realized
that I wouldn't be able
to fight off a man.
Hey, Kiriyama.
What do you want to do?
I'd rather not say.
I want to help.
That's the problem.
If I say anything to you,
I'll be asking for help.
Is that so wrong?
I don't want to cause
other people trouble.
Personally, I think you'll be
more trouble as long as you
have androphobia.
How can you say that?!
I don't want to live like this!
But...
Then let me help you!
You don't want to live like this, right?
That's what you said, right?
I'm going to teach you the
way to defeat any man.
Y-You're kinda scaring me.
Just watch and learn.
Grab me.
Th-That hurts just to watch.
What's wrong with you?
But now you know.
One blow is all it takes to...
I'm back!
Serves you right.
I've never been in more pain in my life.
I thought I was gonna die.
Huh? Taichi, someone's
walking this way.
Hey, shouldn't we hide?
It could be annoying if anyone sees us.
Go on without me.
I'm finished...
Stop trying to play hero!
Uh, that wasn't my intention.
Um, excuse me?
Shoot!
Geez! Hurry up!
Ki-Kiriyama, this should be far enough.
Huh? I guess.
No way. When did I...?
You didn't seem to have a problem doing it.
That's because I was desperate.
Besides, it's just you.
Anyway, what was that about?
Why should a girl have to
experience the pain of a man?
But it worked, right?
I guess, well...
Does that work on every man?
Yeah, it's not just me.
Really...
That kind of pain would
leave them paralyzed.
One blow is all I need to win.
I'll practice at home.
Have I created some kind of
terrible melee weapon?
Say, why did you do that for me?
You even hurt yourself in the process.
Can't I just want to help?
Sounds like something you would say.
Thanks, Taichi.
Yaegashi-kun...
Were you with a girl in the
District 5 park last night?
Wh-What are you talking about?
Were you the person I saw struggling
with a small girl with long hair?
I always pass that park
when I walk our dog.
Y-You've got the wrong person.
Very well.
I may have been seeing things.
I apologize for the false accusation.
And here I was thinking I'd caught
you in the act of cheating.
'Sup, Taichi!
Hey, Kiriyama...
Hey, hey, hey.
C-Could you stop that?
Guess what, Taichi?
I might get back into martial
arts and pro wrestling,
so tell me what you know.
Yeah, you bet.
How about right now?
Not right now. Not right now.
Maybe later.
I need to get going.
You can move on, Kiriyama.
What was that about?
Huh? Whoa!
Did something happen between
the two of you last night?!
That must be it!
I-It wasn't anything special.
I just gave her a little advice.
Well, it's none of my business.
It's definitely my business!
How are you guys so close
after one conversation?!
In that case, let's have a
strategy meeting, Iori-chan!
What? But it's none of my business!
And?
No, it really wasn't anything special.
I just gave Kiriyama a little push.
I guess this personality
swapping business
can actually do some good.
I was convinced that
it would destroy us...
Inaba?
Inaba!
Inaba, what's wrong?
Hey, Inaba!
Inaba!
Do you want to know
more about me, Taichi?
You need to take care of your own body.
I thought he might be responsible.
Am I your enemy?
It's stupid that I'm actually touched.